<odoo>
    <data>
        <template id="aboutus" name="Trademeda AboutUs">
            <xpath expr="." position="inside">
                <link href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css2?family=Source+Sans+Pro:wght@300;400;600;700&amp;display=swap" rel="stylesheet"/>
                <link href="https://fonts.cdnfonts.com/css/helvetica-neue-55" rel="stylesheet"/>
                <link href="https://fonts.cdnfonts.com/css/avenir" rel="stylesheet"/> 
                <link href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css2?family=Merriweather:ital,wght@0,300;0,400;0,700;0,900;1,300;1,400;1,700;1,900&amp;display=swap" rel="stylesheet"/>  
                <link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/5.15.4/css/all.min.css"/>
                <link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="/trademeda/static/src/css/brochure.css"/>
                <link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="/trademeda/static/src/css/aboutus.css"/>

            </xpath>
            <t t-call="trademeda.header"/>
            <div style="background-color: #f6f6f6;padding: 1rem 22%;">
                <main>
                    <!-- <div class="images">
                        <t t-foreach="env['trademeda.aboutus'].sudo().search([],order='sequence')" t-as="aboutus">
                            <t t-if="aboutus.get_image_src()">
                                <div class="image-container">
                                    <img t-att-src="aboutus.get_image_src()" alt="aboutus Image" class="aboutus-image"/>
                                </div>
                            </t>
                        </t>
                        
                    </div> -->
                    <div class="logo">
                        <img src="/trademeda/static/src/img/trademeda_logo1.png"/>
                    </div>
                    <div class="heading">
                        <h4 class="">TRADEMEDA — Empowering trade through wisdom</h4>
                    </div>
                    <div class="">
                        <p class="">TRADEMEDA represents a fusion of two life principles: "Trade" and "Meda."</p>
                        <div class="" style="margin-left:3rem;">
                            <div class=""><b>Trade:</b> This term covers the exchange of goods, services, and value
    between individuals, businesses, and nations. . Trade is an important
    driving force of economic growth. It promotes relationships and
    growing possibilities in the global marketplace.</div>
                        <div class=""><b class="">Meda:</b> Derived from the Greek root "med-" (μηδ-), which signifies
    "wisdom," Meda evokes ideas of thoughtful counsel and strategic
    insight. This is critical to navigate complex business environments.</div>

                        </div>
                    </div>
                    <div class="">Combining these concepts, TRADEMEDA refers to a platform or marketplace that not only facilitates trade but also emphasizes the importance of wisdom and strategic thinking in the trading process. It emphasizes its dedication to training organizations and individuals to make informed choices, optimizing
    their trading activities, and maximize their potential in the marketplace.
    Through this synergy, TRADEMEDA aims to create a more efficient,
    transparent, and successful trading ecosystem.</div>
                    <div class="margin-top">Join us as we chart new territories and fuel progress through the power of
    trade.</div>
                <h4 class="red medium">Welcome to Trademeda:</h4>

                    <p class="red medium">Connecting global businesses with innovative solutions to drive success in today's marketplace.</p>

                    <p>At Trademeda, we are driven by a single mission: to simplify business operations on a global scale. In the ever-evolving landscape of international trade, finding the right partner can be a daunting challenge. That is where our expertise comes into play.</p>

                    <p>Our advanced platform is designed to facilitate perfect connectivity between exporters, importers, traders and manufacturers across the world. We recognize the critical importance of fostering relationships of trust. And we carefully develop robust solutions tailored to a wide range of business needs.</p>
                    <p class="margin-top">By integrating cutting-edge technology with innovative solutions, we offer
    client's access to a dynamic ecosystem that that optimizes operations.
    Whether you are exploring new markets providing high quality suppliers or
    looking for a profitable business opportunity, Trademeda is your trusted
    partner.</p>
                <p class="margin-top">Our unwavering commitment to digital transformation is at the heart of our
    strategy. It helps users imagine, compete, and succeed in global business.
    Together, we will unlock enormous potential and cultivate non-sectoral
    prosperity</p>
                <p class="margin-top">Join us to push boundaries and capitalizing on limitless global
    opportunities. Thank you for choosing Trademeda as your partner in
    success. Let's start the day of moving forward together.
                </p>

                <p class="red margin-top medium bold">Unlock Your Global Potential: Connect, Thrive and Succeed with
    Trademeda!</p>
                <div class="" style="display:flex;gap:1rem">
                    <img src="/trademeda/static/src/img/about1.png"/>
                    <div class="">
                        <p class="">Trademeda is a multifunctional online
    marketing platform designed to support
    business growth through the exchange and
    promotion of products and services. Valuable
    focus on growing your business on a local or
    global level. We connect companies with
    buyers and suppliers of ideas synergize their
    desire to improve their well-being through
    inclusive cooperation</p>
                        <p class="">Unlock your business potential, connects with
    the world, and succeeds in a marketplace
    designed to help you thrive in the digital age.</p>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <p class="red medium center bold">Mission of Trademeda</p>
                <p class="">To simplify business operations globally</p>
                <p class="red medium center bold">Vision of Trademeda</p>
                <p class="">Fuelled by the synergy of technology and innovation, our persistent
    dedication is to optimize efficiency in global trade operations and shape the
    future of commerce infrastructure. We are committed to assisting users in
    envisioning, competing, and thriving in the business arena, with a steadfast
    emphasis on digitization as its foundational element. Together, we unlock
    boundless possibilities and accomplish success within the field of trade.</p>
                <p class="red medium bold">Core Values:</p>
                <p class="">At Trademeda, we believe in synergy, persistence and trade are at the core of
    everything we do. These values drive our operations. From responsibly
    sourcing eco-friendly materials to providing excellent customer support.</p>
                <ul class="">
                    <li>Synergy, persistence, and trade stand as the fundamental
    principles at Trademeda, guiding every decision and action we
    take.</li>
                    <li>These core values act as our operational compass, ensuring the
    conscientious acquisition of eco-friendly materials.</li>
                    <li>We credit both the transformative potential and the unwavering
    commitment of our collaborative efforts</li>
                    <li>From upholding ethical sourcing protocols to establishing
    unmatched service standards, these values shape our business
    philosophy</li>
                    <li>At Trademeda, we are a unique blend of synergy, persistence,
    and trade in maintaining excellence in everything we do.</li>

                </ul>
                <p class="red medium bold">Brand Story:</p>
                <div class="" style="display:flex;gap:1rem">
                    <img src="/trademeda/static/src/img/abhishek.png"/>
                    <p class="">Trademeda originates from the vision of Mr. Abhishek
    Kumar, who is a software engineering graduate. In
    addition to his engineering background, he holds
    postgraduate qualifications in both marketing and
    finance, and has undergone specialized training in
    export-import at the prestigious Indian Institute of
    Foreign Trade in Delhi. He has accumulated extensive
    experience working with export-import companies,
    gaining valuable insights into the challenges faced by
    exporters, importers, and traders in establishing
    reliable business partnerships, both locally and
    internationally.
    Building upon his wealth of experience in the export-import sector, Mr.
    Kumar conceptualized a unified online platform aimed at facilitating
    seamless connections between buyers and suppliers. This platform
    empowers its users by facilitating the swift and efficient discovery of
    products and suppliers for buyers. Additionally, it equips suppliers with
    essential tools to access a global audience for their products</p>
                </div>

                <p class="medium red bold center">Trademeda: Your Trusted Partner in Global Trade</p>
                <div class="flex">
                    <p class="">At Trademeda, we provide a global platform
that facilitates business operations. It
perfectly connects you with certain business
partners. Our mission is to remove the
complexities of international trade. Improve
processes Opening up new opportunities and
expanding market access Increase business
potential in driving long-term growth in the
global market.</p>
                <img src="/trademeda/static/src/img/AU2.jpg"/>
                </div>
                <div class="flex"><p class="red bold">What We Do:</p><p class="blue">“Connecting buyers and suppliers for your business.”</p></div>
                <div class="">
                    <img src="/trademeda/static/src/img/P5.jpg"/>
                </div>
                <div class="">
                    <ul>
                        <li><span class="bold">Global Connectivity &amp; Simplified Trade:</span>We facilitate perfect
connectivity between buyers and suppliers across the world. Doing
business, you can navigate international trade more easily and
expand your horizons.</li>
                        <li><span class="bold">Efficient Discovery of Opportunities:</span>Our platform enables the fast
and efficient discovery of new products, suppliers and business
opportunities, helping users identify and connect with the right
partners quickly.</li>
                        <li><span class="bold">Optimized Trade Processes:</span>We simplify complex business
processes. Reduce layoffs and ensure a quiet and efficient interaction
between buyers and suppliers. To manage the best results for all
parties involved.</li>
                        <li><span class="bold">Enhanced Accessibility &amp; Productivity:</span>By improving access to
global markets, we increase the productivity of both buyers and
suppliers, helping them unlock greater success in the international
marketplace.</li>
                        <li><span class="bold">Expanding Global Market Reach for Suppliers:</span>Suppliers gain
greater visibility and access to a global audience, empowering them to
grow their businesses, reach new markets, and forge valuable
partnerships.</li>
                        <li><span class="bold">Maximizing Growth Opportunities:</span>Trademeda is dedicated to
supporting business growth by offering access to high-quality
partners, new sourcing opportunities, and an expansive global trade
network that drives success.</li>
                        <li><span class="bold">Continuous Platform Evolution:</span>We are committed to constantly
evolving our platform to meet the changing needs of the global trade
ecosystem, offering innovative solutions that help businesses explore
new opportunities and scale to new heights.</li>
                        <li><span class="bold">Inclusive Sourcing Solutions:</span>Trademeda brings together buyers and
suppliers from around the world in a single platform, providing
inclusive sourcing solutions that simplify finding reliable partners and
growing your business globally.</li>
                        <li><span class="bold">Building a Trusted Network:</span>Through our created network of
reputable suppliers and active buyers, we create a trustworthy
environment that fosters transparent communication, secure
negotiations, and successful transactions.</li>

                    </ul>
                </div>
                <p class="">Trademeda is your ideal partner for navigating the global marketplace,
driving business success through seamless connections, secure
transactions, and a continuously evolving platform designed to meet the
demands of modern international trade.</p>
                <p class="bold red medium">Our services:</p>
                <img src="/trademeda/static/src/img/P4.jpg"/>
                <ul>
                    <li><span class="bold">Product Listings:</span>Businesses can list their products for visibility to
potential buyers.</li>
                    <li><span class="bold">Trade Leads:</span>Users can post and respond to inquiries and trade
leads, facilitating direct connections.</li>
                    <li><span class="bold">Supplier Directory:</span>A comprehensive directory to help buyers find
and connect with verified suppliers across various industries.</li>
                    <li><span class="bold">Verified Members:</span>They often provide a verification process to
enhance trust between buyers and suppliers.</li>
                    <li><span class="bold">Online Advertising:</span>Options for businesses to promote their products
and services through various advertising tools.</li>
                    <li><span class="bold">E-commerce Solutions:</span>Services to help businesses set up and
manage online stores.</li>
                </ul>
                <p class="red bold medium">Key features of Trademeda:</p>
                <img src="/trademeda/static/src/img/P3.jpg"/>
                <ul>
                    <li><span class="bold">Global B2B Marketplace:</span>Trademeda serves as a vast online platform
that connects buyers and suppliers from around the globe, facilitating
international trade and fostering business relationships.</li>
                    <li><span class="bold">Buyers and Supplier Directory:</span></li>
                    <li><span class="bold"></span>Users can search for manufacturers,
wholesalers, distributors, exporters, importers and traders by filtering
through product categories, locations, and ratings.</li>
                    <li><span class="bold">Product Listings:</span>Enables suppliers to showcase their products with
comprehensive descriptions, specifications, and images, simplifying
the process for buyers to locate what they require.</li>
                    <li><span class="bold">Company Profiles:</span>Organizations can build comprehensive profiles to
highlight their expertise, certifications, and product offerings,
increasing their visibility.</li>
                    <li><span class="bold">Trade Leads:</span>Provides a platform for submitting and addressing trade
inquiries, assisting businesses in discovering new opportunities.</li>
                    <li><span class="bold">Advanced Search Filters:</span>Allows users to narrow down searches
using specific criteria, including location, product category, and type
of supplier.</li>
                    <li><span class="bold">User-Friendly Interface:</span>Engineered for user-friendliness, our
platform ensures straightforward navigation for both seasoned
professionals and newcomers alike.</li>
                    <li><span class="bold">Request for Quotation (RFQ):</span>Buyers can submit requests for
quotations, enabling suppliers to provide their most competitive offers,
which simplify price comparison.</li>
                    <li><span class="bold">Ready to Buy:</span>Suppliers can showcase product offers, enabling
buyers to connect if the products and prices meet their requirements.</li>
                    <li><span class="bold">Advertise with us:</span>Offers promotional tools and features that assist
businesses in enhancing their visibility on the platform and
connecting with prospective customers.</li>
                    <li><span class="bold">Notifications:</span>Buyers and suppliers are promptly informed of new
arrivals through the “Notify Me” feature on Trademeda's platform,
ensuring they stay updated with the latest offerings.</li>
                    <li><span class="bold">Mobile App:</span>We recognize the importance of mobile applications in
the current business landscape and are committed to offering this
feature in the near future.</li>
                    <li><span class="bold">Discussion forum:</span>Our discussion forum serves as an essential
platform for buyers and suppliers to engage in meaningful
conversations, enhancing collaboration and knowledge sharing within
the trade community. By enabling real-time communication and
efficient problem-solving, this feature reinforces relationships and
promotes continuous improvement in all interactions.</li>

                </ul>
                <p class="bold red medium">Key Benefits and Value Proposition of Trademeda:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li><span class="bold">Global Market Access:</span>Trademeda brings together exporters,
importers, traders, manufacturers, and wholesalers, making
international trade and market expansion seamless. Our platform
connects businesses with millions of buyers and suppliers globally, unlocking new opportunities for growth. With minimal investment,
companies can efficiently scale and extend their reach using
Trademeda's affordable and effective solutions.</li>
                    <div class="flex">
                        <div class="">
                        
                            <li><span class="bold">Wide Industry Coverage:</span>The platform supports
businesses from a wide range
of industries, including
agriculture, textiles,
electronics, machinery,
Computers and more,
providing opportunities for
companies in diverse sectors.</li>
                            <li><span class="bold">Verified Buyers and Suppliers:</span>The platform
ensures credibility by
verifying the legitimacy of
businesses, which reduces
the risk of fraud and fosters
trust between trading
partners.</li>
                            <li><span class="bold">Comprehensive Product Listings:</span>Businesses can list
their products with detailed
descriptions, photos, and
specifications, making it
easier for buyers to find
exactly what they are looking
for and make informed
decisions.</li>
                            <li><span class="bold">Easy Access to Trade Leads:</span>Trademeda provides real-time access to
thousands of trade leads across various industries, enabling
businesses to find relevant opportunities quickly and easily.</li>
                        </div>
                        <img src="/trademeda/static/src/img/P2.jpg" style="max-height: 50vh;"/>

                    </div>
                    <li><span class="bold">Tailored Membership Plans:</span>The platform offers free and premium
membership options. Premium members gain access to exclusive
features like direct buyer inquiries, priority support, and higher
visibility in search results.</li>
                    <li><span class="bold">Efficient Communication Tools:</span>Integrated communication tools
allow buyers and sellers to interact securely on the platform,
streamlining negotiations and fostering transparent transactions.</li>
                    <li><span class="bold">User-Friendly Interface:</span>The platform is designed to be intuitive and
easy to navigate, allowing users to search for products, send inquiries,
and connect with suppliers effortlessly.</li>
                    <li><span class="bold">Mobile Applications:</span>A mobile app provides users with seamless, on-
the-go access to products or services, enhancing convenience,

engagement, and customer loyalty through personalized experiences
and real-time interactions.</li>
                </ul>
                <p class="red medium bold">Why Choose Trademeda?</p>

                <div class="flex">
                    <img src="/trademeda/static/src/img/P1.jpg" style="max-height: 50vh;max-width:50%;"/>

                    <div class="">
                        <ul>
                            <li><span class="bold">Innovative &amp; Evolving Platform:</span> Our platform is continuously accelerating to
meet the dynamic needs of the global
business ecosystem. This ensures that your
company always has access to the latest
technology and solutions for success.</li>
                            <li><span class="bold">Global Reach with Local Impact:</span> Trademeda connects buyers and suppliers
from all over the world. Continuously build

an integrated platform that promotes cross-
border collaboration. While also meeting the

needs of the local market.</li>
                            <li><span class="bold">Trusted Network:</span> We offer access to
a carefully selected network of trusted
buyers and suppliers. Fostering reliable
long-term business relationships to
guarantee high-quality connections.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <p class="">Trademeda is your ideal partner for global marketing consulting. Our
platform helps companies grow, succeed and thrive internationally. Join us
today and experience the future of two global businesses.</p>
                <p class="red medium bold">Contact Us:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li><span class="bold">E-mail:</span> info@trademeda.com</li>
                    <li><span class="bold">Phone no.:</span> +91-7033295727</li>
                </ul>
                </main>
            </div>
        </template>
    </data>
</odoo>
    