<odoo>
    <data>
        <template id="privacyPolicy" name="Trademeda Privacy Policy">
         <xpath expr="." position="inside">
            <link href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css2?family=Source+Sans+Pro:wght@300;400;600;700&amp;display=swap" rel="stylesheet"/>
            <link href="https://fonts.cdnfonts.com/css/helvetica-neue-55" rel="stylesheet"/>
            <link href="https://fonts.cdnfonts.com/css/avenir" rel="stylesheet"/> 
            <link href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css2?family=Merriweather:ital,wght@0,300;0,400;0,700;0,900;1,300;1,400;1,700;1,900&amp;display=swap" rel="stylesheet"/>  
            <link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="/trademeda/static/src/css/privacyPolicy.css"/>
            <link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/5.15.4/css/all.min.css"/>
        </xpath>

        <t t-call="trademeda.header"/>
        <main class="">
            <!-- <h1 class="">Privacy Policy</h1>
            <p>This Privacy Policy explains Trademeda.com&#39;s dedication to protecting your privacy. By using this website, you agree to the terms described here.</p>
            <p>Trademeda, the company behind this website, values your privacy. We use your personal information solely to manage your account and deliver the services you request, such as B2B trade connections.</p>
            <div class="subheading">Communication and Information Sharing</div>
             -->


            <div class="container">

                <h1>Privacy Policy</h1>

                <p class="list-item">This Privacy Policy explains Trademeda.com's dedication to protecting your privacy.
By using this website, you agree to the terms described here.</p>

                <p class="list-item">Trademeda, the company behind this website, values your privacy. We use your
personal information solely to manage your account and deliver the services you
request, such as B2B trade connections.</p>



                <h2>Communication and Information Sharing</h2>

                <p class="list-item">Occasionally, we may reach out with promotions and updates via mail, email, phone,
text messages, and automated calls. As a business advertising platform, we may also
share your details with potential business partners. Non-registered users cannot access
your contact information but can send inquiries through our system.</p>


                <h2>1. Collection of Information</h2>

                <p class="list-item">I. Business Information: This includes contact details, company profile, trade leads,
buy leads, catalogs, and inquiries collected during registration, newsletter subscriptions, email
communications, feedback, or surveys.</p>

                <p class="list-item">II. Payment Information: Data related to payments made via credit card, cheque, or
bank transfer, such as name, address, email, phone number, credit card number, CVV, and bank
details.</p>

                <p class="list-item">III. Information like visitor IP addresses, browser software,
operating systems, and pages viewed.</p>

                <p class="list-item">These are collectively referred to as "Information Gathered."</p>


                <h2>2. Use and Sharing of Information:</h2>

                <p class="list-item">i. This information is made public to maximize your business reach and
may be shared with authorized agents and verification agencies.</p>

                <p class="list-item">ii. Payment Information: We do not disclose this information unless required by law. Credit card
information is processed directly by payment gateways and is not stored on our site.</p>

                <p class="list-item">iii. Statistical Information: Collected to enhance our services and manage site performance, this
data is shared in aggregate form without personal details.</p>


                <h2>3. Disclosure of Information</h2>

                <p class="list-item">We may disclose "Information Gathered" if legally required or if withholding it would
harm our or our users' interests.</p>


                <h2>4. Modifying or Deleting Your Information</h2>

                <p class="list-item">i. Modify your business information by logging into your account..</p>

                <p class="list-item">ii. Request deletion of your information via the "terminate membership" option in your profile or by
contacting us directly.</p>

                <p class="list-item">iii. We typically process removal requests within 48-72 business hours.</p>


                <h2>5. Duration of Information Storage</h2>

                <p class="list-item">Your public profile remains online indefinitely unless you request its removal.</p>


                <h2>6. Hyperlinks to Other Websites</h2>

                <p class="list-item">Our site may include links to third-party websites. We recommend reviewing their
privacy policies and terms of use, as we are not responsible for their content or
services.</p>


                <h2>7. Cookies</h2>

                <p class="list-item">We use cookies to recognize you on our website, a common practice for login-based
sites.</p>


                <h2>8. Data Security</h2>

                <p class="list-item">We implement measures to protect your data, but by using this site, you waive any
claims against us for the loss, alteration, or misuse of information.</p>


                <h2>9. Revisions to This Policy</h2>

                <p class="list-item">This Privacy Policy may change over time. Review it regularly for updates, as
continued use of the site implies acceptance of any changes.</p>


                <h2>10. Jurisdiction and Applicable Law</h2>

                <p class="list-item">Any disputes regarding this Privacy Policy will be governed by the laws of India, and
fall under the jurisdiction of Civil court of Patna, Bihar,India.</p>


                <h2>Contact Information</h2>

                <p class="list-item">For questions, comments, or incident reports, contact us at:</p>

                <p class="list-item">Trademeda</p>

                <p class="list-item">B-96, P.C. Colony, Lohia nagar, Kankarbagh, Patna, Bihar- 800020,INDIA</p>

                <p class="list-item">Phone: +91-70332 95727</p>
            </div>
        </main>
        </template>
    </data>
</odoo>