<odoo>
    <data>
        <template id="product_listing" name="Product Listing">
            <xpath expr="." position="inside">
                <link href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css2?family=Source+Sans+Pro:wght@300;400;600;700&amp;display=swap" rel="stylesheet"/>
                <link href="https://fonts.cdnfonts.com/css/helvetica-neue-55" rel="stylesheet"/>
                <link href="https://fonts.cdnfonts.com/css/avenir" rel="stylesheet"/> 
                <link href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css2?family=Merriweather:ital,wght@0,300;0,400;0,700;0,900;1,300;1,400;1,700;1,900&amp;display=swap" rel="stylesheet"/>  
                <link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/5.15.4/css/all.min.css"/>
                <link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="/trademeda/static/src/css/brochure.css"/>
                <link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="/trademeda/static/src/css/aboutus.css"/>

            </xpath>
            <t t-call="trademeda.header"/>
            <main>
                <h1 style="color:#07407a;">Product Listing Policy</h1>
                <p>This Product Listing Policy explains the rules for listing products on Trademeda.com.
Please review it carefully before registering your products on our site.</p>
                <p>1. You must not list, sell, or purchase any items on Trademeda.com that are banned
or restricted by any federal, state, or local law in any country.</p>
                <p>2. The platform prohibits the trade of illegal products, items that infringe on
intellectual property rights, or those that could easily be used for illegal purposes.</p>
                <p>3. As a user of Trademeda, it is your responsibility to ensure the legality and
permissibility of your listed products. Before adding any product, selling lead, or
buying lead, you must confirm that your items comply with this policy.
Trademeda has the right to remove any listings that violate these terms without
prior notice and may disable accounts of users who repeatedly breach the policy
after receiving warnings.</p>
                <p class="bold">Prohibited Products</p>
                <p>This section details items that are strictly forbidden on Trademeda.com:</p>
                <ul>
                    <p class="bold">1. Alcoholic Beverages</p>
                    <li>The platform prohibits the sale of alcoholic beverages, including beer,
wine, whisky, gin, vodka, and rum.</li>
                </ul>
                <ul>
                    <p class="bold">2. Tobacco Products</p>
                    <li>There is complete prohibition on sale of cigars, cigarettes, pipe
tobacco, hookah tobacco, and chewing tobacco.</li>
                    <li>While electronic cigarettes and accessories are permitted, nicotine and
other e-liquids are banned.</li>
                </ul>
                <ul>
                    <p class="bold">3. Medical Drugs and Devices</p>
                    <li>Prescription medications, psychotropic drugs, and narcotics are not
permitted.</li>
                    <li>Sexual enhancement foods and supplementstaken orally are banned.</li>
                    <li>The sale of unapproved drugs and medical devices is not allowed.</li>
                </ul>
                <ul>
                    <p class="bold">4. Illegal Drugs and Paraphernalia</p>
                    <li>The platform strictly bans the sale of narcotics, tranquilizers,
psychotropic substances, both natural and synthetic drugs, steroids, and other
controlled substances.</li>
                    <li>Selling chemicals used in the production of drugs is also prohibited.</li>
                </ul>
                <ul>
                    <p class="bold">5. Precious Metals</p>
                    <li>The trade of gold, silver, and other precious metals (excluding jewelry) is
banned.</li>
                    <li>Rough diamonds and "conflict minerals" from countries that do not
comply with international regulations are forbidden.</li>
                </ul>
                <ul>
                    <p class="bold">6. Wildlife and Animal Products</p>
                    <li>Products derived from wildlife, including pelts, skins, organs, teeth,
claws, shells, bones, tusks, ivory, and similar items, are prohibited.</li>
                </ul>
                <ul>
                    <p class="bold">7. Financial Services</p>
                    <li>Services such as money transfers, bank guarantees, letters of
credit, loans, fundraising, and personal investment services are not allowed.</li>
                </ul>
                <ul>
                    <p class="bold">Other Prohibited Items</p>
                    <li>Counterfeit currency and stamps</li>
                    <li>Adult subscription or chatting services, contracts, and tickets are banned.</li>
                    <li>Pornographic, erotic, and adult content, including pictures, videos,
DVDs, magazines, toys, etc., is prohibited.</li>
                    <li>Credit card services, credit repair services, applications for financial
services or loans, and collection services are not allowed.</li>
                    <li>The sale of mailing lists and personal information is not allowed.</li>
                    <li>Items promoting hatred, racism, religious persecution, or products
featuring nudity are not allowed</li>
                    <li>Weapons such as firearms, ammunition, high-capacity magazines, stun
guns, air guns, and military weapons are prohibited.</li>
                    <li>Human body parts, fluids, and remains are not permitted.</li>
                    <li>Job postings, lottery, raffle, and contest-related items are banned..</li>
                    <li>Requests for donations are banned.</li>
                    <li>Items that are Sanctioned and prohibited by regulations and authorities
are not allowed.</li>
                    <li>Unauthorized software, OEM or bundled software, spyware,
spamware, e-mail advertising, opt-in, or any commercial messaging services
are banned.</li>
                </ul>
                <ul>
                    <p class="bold">9. Restricted Countries</p>
                    <li>Trademeda prohibits users from countries listed on US and
international sanctions lists. Accounts from these regions will be deleted
without prior notice.</li>
                </ul>
                <p>By listing products on Trademeda.com, you agree to abide by this Product Listing
Policy. Failure to comply may result in the removal of your listings and the
suspension or termination of your account.</p>
                <p class="bold">
                10. Use of foul language, abusive language, harassment, bullying, hate speech,
sexually implied content or any other type of language, content or action on
Chatting, Discussion Forum or any other space on this website, which is
prohibited by the law is strictly prohibited on this platform.</p>
            </main>
        </template>
    </data>
</odoo>
