<odoo>
    <data>
        <template id="trustscore" name="Trademeda Trust Score">
         <xpath expr="." position="inside">
            <link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="/trademeda/static/src/css/subcategories.css"/>
            <link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/5.15.4/css/all.min.css"/>
            <link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="/trademeda/static/src/css/aboutus.css"/>

        </xpath>

        <t t-call="trademeda.header"/>
        <main>
            <h3 class="">Trademeda Trust Score: Key Insights</h3>
            <h3>What is Your Trust Score?</h3>
            <p>Your Trust Score on Trademeda indicates the credibility and reliability of your
business in the eyes of potential partners. A higher score significantly boosts your
chances of securing valuable business opportunities. You can improve your Trust
Score by verifying your account, maintaining a detailed and up-to-date profile,
presenting a thorough product catalog, and earning positive reviews from users you
interact with.</p>
            <h3>How is the Trust Score Calculated?</h3>
            <p>The Trust Score is determined by a combination of buyer feedback, peer ratings, and
the longevity of your account on the platform. While a perfect score of 10 is
uncommon, there’s no need to worry if your score begins low. By regularly updating
your profile, providing accurate information, and avoiding negative feedback, your
Trust Score will gradually improve. Below are the key factors that contribute to your
score.</p>
        <ul><p class="bold">Factors for Earning Trust Points</p>
            <li>Receiving positive feedback and ratings from your peers.</li>
            <li>Uploading relevant documentation and receiving ratings for it.</li>
            <li>Verifying your profile by submitting necessary company documentation.</li>
            <li>Listing products with high-quality images, detailed descriptions, and clear
pricing.</li>
            <li>The duration of your active profile on Trademeda.</li>
            <li>Maintaining an active and uninterrupted Premium membership.</li>
        </ul>
        <ul><p class="bold">Factors for Losing Trust Points</p>
            <li>Receiving negative feedback or low ratings from peers.</li>
        </ul>
        <h3>Why Your Trust Score Matters</h3>
        <p>Your Trust Score is an essential measure of your business’s reliability and
trustworthiness. It plays a significant role in attracting inquiries from potential buyers
on Trademeda. Moreover, your Trust Score positions you relative to other
businesses on the platform: higher scores lead to better visibility in search results,
resulting in greater opportunities for growth and business success.</p>
        </main>
        </template>
    </data>
</odoo>